oldnanny.com 2017-07-15

# Oldnanny.com - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy and Data Protection**

This notice discloses the online information practices for Oldnanny.com in order to better protect your privacy. 

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**    
The information collected or submitted applies to Oldnanny.com. By purchasing a membership to Oldnanny.com you must first complete the registration form. During registration you are required to give certain information such as name, email address, etc. 

We use third party payment processing services like CCBill, Epoch, who will obtain additional information such as your address, and credit card data.  
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

We might share information as provied by you with third party service providers to manage certain aspects of the services we provide, such as payments, or maintaining of the Site.

All credit card infos are submitted directly to the credit card companies and are not stored on our servers. The payment process is secured and encrypted. 

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**    
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website.

**Security**    
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to our third party payment processing services in a secure way. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. 

**Cookies**    
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

**Links**    
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Surveys & Contests**   
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Updates**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email support@mediacanarias.net**
